sentence_id,token,label
1,We,O
1,are,O
1,looking,O
1,for,O
1,a,O
1,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
1,Scientist,I-JOB_TITLE
1,to,O
1,join,O
1,our,O
1,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
1,office,O
1,.,O
1,The,O
1,ideal,O
1,candidate,O
1,has,O
1,experience,O
1,with,O
1,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
1,",",O
1,SQL,B-TOOL
1,",",O
1,and,O
1,machine,B-SKILL_TECH
1,learning,I-SKILL_TECH
1,frameworks,O
1,like,O
1,TensorFlow,B-FRAMEWORK
1,or,O
1,PyTorch,B-FRAMEWORK
1,.,O
1,Employment,O
1,type,O
1,is,O
1,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
1,.,O
2,Infosys,B-COMPANY
2,is,O
2,hiring,O
2,a,O
2,Software,B-JOB_TITLE
2,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
2,with,O
2,strong,O
2,Java,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
2,and,O
2,Spring,B-FRAMEWORK
2,Framework,I-FRAMEWORK
2,knowledge,O
2,.,O
2,The,O
2,role,O
2,is,O
2,based,O
2,in,O
2,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
2,and,O
2,requires,O
2,good,O
2,communication,B-SKILL_TECH
2,skills,I-SKILL_TECH
2,.,O
2,Employment,O
2,type,O
2,:,O
2,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
2,.,O
3,Amazon,B-COMPANY
3,is,O
3,seeking,O
3,a,O
3,Backend,B-JOB_TITLE
3,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
3,skilled,O
3,in,O
3,Node.js,B-FRAMEWORK
3,",",O
3,AWS,B-TOOL
3,and,O
3,Docker,B-TOOL
3,.,O
3,This,O
3,position,O
3,is,O
3,located,O
3,in,O
3,Chennai,B-LOCATION
3,.,O
3,Candidates,O
3,with,O
3,1-2,O
3,years,O
3,of,O
3,experience,O
3,are,O
3,preferred,O
3,.,O
3,Employment,O
3,type,O
3,:,O
3,contract,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
3,.,O
4,We,O
4,need,O
4,a,O
4,Frontend,B-JOB_TITLE
4,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
4,proficient,O
4,in,O
4,React,B-FRAMEWORK
4,",",O
4,JavaScript,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
4,",",O
4,and,O
4,HTML,B-TOOL
4,/,I-TOOL
4,CSS,I-TOOL
4,.,O
4,The,O
4,company,O
4,is,O
4,TCS,B-COMPANY
4,",",O
4,and,O
4,the,O
4,job,O
4,location,O
4,is,O
4,Pune,B-LOCATION
4,.,O
4,Employment,O
4,type,O
4,:,O
4,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
4,.,O
5,Google,B-COMPANY
5,is,O
5,hiring,O
5,a,O
5,Machine,B-JOB_TITLE
5,Learning,I-JOB_TITLE
5,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
5,.,O
5,Required,O
5,skills,O
5,include,O
5,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
5,",",O
5,TensorFlow,B-FRAMEWORK
5,",",O
5,and,O
5,SQL,B-TOOL
5,.,O
5,This,O
5,role,O
5,is,O
5,remote,B-LOCATION
5,.,O
5,Employment,O
5,type,O
5,:,O
5,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
5,.,O
6,Wipro,B-COMPANY
6,is,O
6,looking,O
6,for,O
6,a,O
6,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
6,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
6,skilled,O
6,in,O
6,Excel,B-TOOL
6,",",O
6,Tableau,B-TOOL
6,",",O
6,and,O
6,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
6,.,O
6,The,O
6,role,O
6,is,O
6,based,O
6,in,O
6,Noida,B-LOCATION
6,.,O
6,Employment,O
6,type,O
6,:,O
6,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
6,.,O
7,Job,O
7,location,O
7,:,O
7,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
7,.,O
7,Employment,O
7,type,O
7,:,O
7,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
7,.,O
8,IBM,B-COMPANY
8,is,O
8,hiring,O
8,a,O
8,Cloud,B-JOB_TITLE
8,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
8,experienced,O
8,in,O
8,AWS,B-TOOL
8,",",O
8,Docker,B-TOOL
8,",",O
8,and,O
8,Kubernetes,B-TOOL
8,.,O
8,The,O
8,role,O
8,is,O
8,based,O
8,in,O
8,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
8,.,O
8,Employment,O
8,type,O
8,:,O
8,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
8,.,O
9,Accenture,B-COMPANY
9,seeks,O
9,a,O
9,DevOps,B-JOB_TITLE
9,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
9,skilled,O
9,in,O
9,Jenkins,B-TOOL
9,",",O
9,Git,B-TOOL
9,",",O
9,and,O
9,Linux,B-TOOL
9,.,O
9,The,O
9,job,O
9,is,O
9,located,O
9,in,O
9,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
9,.,O
9,Employment,O
9,type,O
9,:,O
9,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
9,.,O
10,HCL,B-COMPANY
10,is,O
10,looking,O
10,for,O
10,a,O
10,Software,B-JOB_TITLE
10,Tester,I-JOB_TITLE
10,proficient,O
10,in,O
10,Selenium,B-TOOL
10,and,O
10,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
10,.,O
10,This,O
10,role,O
10,is,O
10,based,O
10,in,O
10,Chennai,B-LOCATION
10,.,O
10,Employment,O
10,type,O
10,:,O
10,contract,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
10,.,O
11,We,O
11,are,O
11,hiring,O
11,a,O
11,UI/UX,B-JOB_TITLE
11,Designer,I-JOB_TITLE
11,with,O
11,experience,O
11,in,O
11,Figma,B-TOOL
11,",",O
11,Adobe,B-TOOL
11,XD,I-TOOL
11,",",O
11,and,O
11,prototyping,B-SKILL_TECH
11,tools,I-SKILL_TECH
11,.,O
11,Company,O
11,:,O
11,Zoho,B-COMPANY
11,.,O
11,Location,O
11,:,O
11,Chennai,B-LOCATION
11,.,O
11,Employment,O
11,type,O
11,:,O
11,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
11,.,O
12,Flipkart,B-COMPANY
12,is,O
12,hiring,O
12,a,O
12,Product,B-JOB_TITLE
12,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
12,with,O
12,strong,O
12,soft,B-SKILL_TECH
12,skills,I-SKILL_TECH
12,and,O
12,experience,O
12,in,O
12,market,B-SKILL_TECH
12,analysis,I-SKILL_TECH
12,.,O
12,Location,O
12,:,O
12,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
12,.,O
12,Employment,O
12,type,O
12,:,O
12,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
12,.,O
13,We,O
13,need,O
13,an,O
13,Android,B-JOB_TITLE
13,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
13,with,O
13,Java,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
13,",",O
13,Kotlin,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
13,",",O
13,and,O
13,Android,B-TOOL
13,Studio,I-TOOL
13,expertise,O
13,.,O
13,Company,O
13,:,O
13,Samsung,B-COMPANY
13,.,O
13,Location,O
13,:,O
13,Delhi,B-LOCATION
13,.,O
13,Employment,O
13,type,O
13,:,O
13,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
13,.,O
14,Microsoft,B-COMPANY
14,is,O
14,hiring,O
14,a,O
14,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
14,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
14,skilled,O
14,in,O
14,SQL,B-TOOL
14,",",O
14,Azure,B-TOOL
14,",",O
14,and,O
14,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
14,.,O
14,This,O
14,position,O
14,is,O
14,located,O
14,in,O
14,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
14,.,O
14,Employment,O
14,type,O
14,:,O
14,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
14,.,O
15,We,O
15,are,O
15,looking,O
15,for,O
15,a,O
15,Cybersecurity,B-JOB_TITLE
15,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
15,experienced,O
15,with,O
15,Linux,B-TOOL
15,",",O
15,SIEM,B-TOOL
15,tools,I-TOOL
15,",",O
15,and,O
15,network,B-SKILL_TECH
15,security,I-SKILL_TECH
15,.,O
15,Company,O
15,:,O
15,EY,B-COMPANY
15,.,O
15,Location,O
15,:,O
15,Pune,B-LOCATION
15,.,O
15,Employment,O
15,type,O
15,:,O
15,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
15,.,O
16,Oracle,B-COMPANY
16,is,O
16,hiring,O
16,a,O
16,Database,B-JOB_TITLE
16,Administrator,I-JOB_TITLE
16,with,O
16,strong,O
16,SQL,B-TOOL
16,and,O
16,PL/SQL,B-TOOL
16,knowledge,O
16,.,O
16,Location,O
16,:,O
16,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
16,.,O
16,Employment,O
16,type,O
16,:,O
16,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
16,.,O
17,We,O
17,need,O
17,a,O
17,Mobile,B-JOB_TITLE
17,App,I-JOB_TITLE
17,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
17,with,O
17,Flutter,B-FRAMEWORK
17,",",O
17,Dart,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
17,",",O
17,and,O
17,Firebase,B-TOOL
17,experience,O
17,.,O
17,Company,O
17,:,O
17,Swiggy,B-COMPANY
17,.,O
17,Location,O
17,:,O
17,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
17,.,O
17,Employment,O
17,type,O
17,:,O
17,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
17,.,O
18,We,O
18,are,O
18,looking,O
18,for,O
18,a,O
18,Research,B-JOB_TITLE
18,Intern,I-JOB_TITLE
18,pursuing,O
18,a,O
18,Bachelor's,B-EDUCATION_LEVEL
18,degree,O
18,in,O
18,Computer,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
18,Science,I-DEGREE_MAJOR
18,.,O
18,Company,O
18,:,O
18,Adobe,B-COMPANY
18,.,O
18,Location,O
18,:,O
18,Noida,B-LOCATION
18,.,O
18,Employment,O
18,type,O
18,:,O
18,internship,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
18,.,O
19,Cisco,B-COMPANY
19,is,O
19,hiring,O
19,a,O
19,Network,B-JOB_TITLE
19,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
19,with,O
19,CCNA,B-TOOL
19,certification,O
19,and,O
19,strong,O
19,routing/switching,B-SKILL_TECH
19,knowledge,O
19,.,O
19,Location,O
19,:,O
19,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
19,.,O
19,Employment,O
19,type,O
19,:,O
19,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
19,.,O
20,We,O
20,need,O
20,a,O
20,Full,B-JOB_TITLE
20,Stack,I-JOB_TITLE
20,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
20,experienced,O
20,in,O
20,React,B-FRAMEWORK
20,",",O
20,Node.js,B-FRAMEWORK
20,",",O
20,and,O
20,MongoDB,B-TOOL
20,.,O
20,Company,O
20,:,O
20,Paytm,B-COMPANY
20,.,O
20,Location,O
20,:,O
20,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
20,.,O
20,Employment,O
20,type,O
20,:,O
20,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
20,.,O
