sentence_id,token,label
21,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
21,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
21,Responsible,O
21,for,O
21,analyzing,O
21,transactional,O
21,datasets,O
21,to,O
21,identify,O
21,patterns,O
21,&,O
21,metrics,O
21,Requires,O
21,proficiency,O
21,in,O
21,SQL,B-SKILL_TECH
21,Tableau,B-TOOL
21,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
21,predictive,O
21,modeling,O
21,and,O
21,risk,O
21,dashboards,O
21,Qualifications,O
21,include,O
21,Bachelor,B-EDUCATION_LEVEL
21,'s,I-EDUCATION_LEVEL
21,in,O
21,Statistics,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
21,or,O
21,Data,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
21,Science,I-DEGREE_MAJOR
21,.,O
21,Hybrid,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
21,role,O
21,located,O
21,in,O
21,Pune,B-LOCATION
21,at,O
21,Razorpay,B-COMPANY
21,.,O

22,Cloud,B-JOB_TITLE
22,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
22,Hiring,O
22,for,O
22,AWS,B-SKILL_TECH
22,focused,O
22,to,O
22,automate,O
22,infrastructure,O
22,using,O
22,Terraform,B-TOOL
22,Docker,B-TOOL
22,Kubernetes,B-TOOL
22,Full,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
22,time,I-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
22,position,O
22,at,O
22,Infosys,B-COMPANY
22,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
22,Must,O
22,know,O
22,CI/CD,B-SKILL_TECH
22,pipelines,O
22,Lambda,B-SKILL_TECH
22,CloudWatch,B-TOOL
22,.,O

23,iOS,B-JOB_TITLE
23,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
23,Working,O
23,on,O
23,native,O
23,iOS,B-SKILL_TECH
23,applications,O
23,in,O
23,SwiftUI,B-FRAMEWORK
23,.,O
23,Familiarity,O
23,with,O
23,XCode,B-TOOL
23,Combine,B-SKILL_TECH
23,CoreData,B-SKILL_TECH
23,API,B-SKILL_TECH
23,integration,O
23,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
23,Accenture,B-COMPANY

24,Cybersecurity,B-JOB_TITLE
24,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
24,Join,O
24,Palo,B-COMPANY
24,Alto,I-COMPANY
24,Networks,I-COMPANY
24,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
24,Security,B-JOB_TITLE
24,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
24,SIEM,B-TOOL
24,IDS/IPS,B-TOOL
24,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
24,B.Tech,B-EDUCATION_LEVEL
24,Cyber,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
24,Security,I-DEGREE_MAJOR
24,Computer,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
24,Science,I-DEGREE_MAJOR

25,Mechanical,B-JOB_TITLE
25,CAD,I-JOB_TITLE
25,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
25,SolidWorks,B-TOOL
25,AutoCAD,B-TOOL
25,Tata,B-COMPANY
25,Motors,I-COMPANY
25,Pune,B-LOCATION
25,full,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
25,time,I-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
