sentence_id,token,label
26,UI,B-JOB_TITLE
26,/,I-JOB_TITLE
26,UX,I-JOB_TITLE
26,Designer,I-JOB_TITLE
26,required,O
26,to,O
26,create,O
26,interactive,O
26,web,O
26,and,O
26,mobile,O
26,interface,O
26,designs,O
26,.,O
26,Must,O
26,be,O
26,proficient,O
26,in,O
26,Figma,B-TOOL
26,,,O
26,design,B-SKILL_TECH
26,systems,I-SKILL_TECH
26,,,O
26,wireframing,B-SKILL_TECH
26,,,O
26,prototyping,B-SKILL_TECH
26,and,O
26,user-flow,B-SKILL_TECH
26,mapping,I-SKILL_TECH
26,.,O
26,Preferred,O
26,experience,O
26,in,O
26,usability,B-SKILL_TECH
26,testing,I-SKILL_TECH
26,and,O
26,heuristic,B-SKILL_TECH
26,evaluation,I-SKILL_TECH
26,.,O
26,Remote,B-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE
26,role,O
26,at,O
26,Zomato,B-COMPANY
26,.,O

27,Backend,B-JOB_TITLE
27,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
27,with,O
27,experience,O
27,in,O
27,Node.js,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
27,,,O
27,Express,B-FRAMEWORK
27,,,O
27,RESTful,B-SKILL_TECH
27,APIs,I-SKILL_TECH
27,,,O
27,MongoDB,B-DATABASE
27,and,O
27,Redis,B-DATABASE
27,caching,O
27,.,O
27,Experience,O
27,with,O
27,microservices,B-SKILL_TECH
27,architecture,I-SKILL_TECH
27,and,O
27,Kafka,B-TOOL
27,streaming,O
27,preferred,O
27,.,O
27,Full,B-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE
27,time,I-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE
27,at,O
27,Flipkart,B-COMPANY
27,.,O
27,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
27,.,O

28,Machine,B-JOB_TITLE
28,Learning,I-JOB_TITLE
28,Intern,I-JOB_TITLE
28,responsible,O
28,for,O
28,model,O
28,experimentation,O
28,,,O
28,feature,B-SKILL_TECH
28,extraction,I-SKILL_TECH
28,,,O
28,dataset,B-SKILL_TECH
28,preprocessing,I-SKILL_TECH
28,and,O
28,ML,B-SKILL_TECH
28,pipeline,I-SKILL_TECH
28,setup,I-SKILL_TECH
28,.,O
28,Required,O
28,skills,O
28,:,O
28,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
28,scikit-learn,B-LIBRARY
28,NumPy,B-LIBRARY
28,pandas,B-LIBRARY
28,matplotlib,B-LIBRARY
28,.,O
28,Duration,O
28,6,B-DURATION
28,months,I-DURATION
28,internship,I-DURATION
28,.,O
28,Work-from-home,B-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE
28,available,O

29,Robotics,B-JOB_TITLE
29,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
29,with,O
29,experience,O
29,in,O
29,C++,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
29,ROS,B-TOOL
29,SLAM,B-SKILL_TECH
29,LiDAR,B-TOOL
29,mapping,O
29,and,O
29,embedded,B-SKILL_TECH
29,control,I-SKILL_TECH
29,systems,I-SKILL_TECH
29,.,O
29,Work,O
29,involves,O
29,developing,O
29,robotic,O
29,navigation,B-SKILL_TECH
29,algorithms,I-SKILL_TECH
29,.,O
29,Chennai,B-LOCATION
29,.,O
29,Boston,B-COMPANY
29,Dynamics,I-COMPANY
29,(,O
29,R&D,B-DEPARTMENT
29,Lab,I-DEPARTMENT
29,),O

30,Technical,B-JOB_TITLE
30,Writer,I-JOB_TITLE
30,for,O
30,API,B-SKILL_TECH
30,documentation,I-SKILL_TECH
30,,,O
30,product,B-SKILL_TECH
30,manuals,I-SKILL_TECH
30,,,O
30,release,B-SKILL_TECH
30,notes,I-SKILL_TECH
30,and,O
30,help-center,B-SKILL_TECH
30,articles,I-SKILL_TECH
30,.,O
30,Required,O
30,tools,O
30,:,O
30,Markdown,B-TOOL
30,Confluence,B-TOOL
30,Git,B-TOOL
30,.,O
30,Bachelor,B-EDUCATION_LEVEL
30,'s,I-EDUCATION_LEVEL
30,in,O
30,English,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
30,,O
30,Journalism,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
30,,O
30,or,O
30,relevant,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
30,field,I-DEGREE_MAJOR
30,.,O
30,Freshworks,B-COMPANY
30,Chennai,B-LOCATION

31,Full-Stack,B-JOB_TITLE
31,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
31,skilled,O
31,in,O
31,Angular,B-FRAMEWORK
31,and,O
31,Spring,B-FRAMEWORK
31,Boot,I-FRAMEWORK
31,.,O
31,MySQL,B-DATABASE
31,required,O
31,.,O
31,Azure,B-TOOL
31,DevOps,I-TOOL
31,CI/CD,B-SKILL_TECH
31,plus,O
31,.,O
31,HCL,B-COMPANY
31,Noida,B-LOCATION

32,Blockchain,B-JOB_TITLE
32,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
32,skilled,O
32,in,O
32,Solidity,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
32,smart,B-SKILL_TECH
32,contracts,I-SKILL_TECH
32,,,O
32,Web3.js,B-LIBRARY
32,,,O
32,Ethereum,B-TECH_PLATFORM
32,testnets,I-TECH_PLATFORM
32,and,O
32,cryptographic,B-SKILL_TECH
32,security,I-SKILL_TECH
32,.,O
32,Remote,B-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE
32,contract,O
32,role,O
32,with,O
32,Polygon,B-COMPANY
32,Labs,I-COMPANY

33,Android,B-JOB_TITLE
33,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
33,with,O
33,Kotlin,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
33,,,O
33,Jetpack,B-FRAMEWORK
33,Compose,I-FRAMEWORK
33,,,O
33,Firebase,B-TOOL
33,integration,O
33,and,O
33,MVVM,B-ARCHITECTURE
33,experience,O
33,.,O
33,Paytm,B-COMPANY
33,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION

34,Unity,B-JOB_TITLE
34,Game,I-JOB_TITLE
34,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
34,with,O
34,Unity3D,B-TOOL
34,,,O
34,C#,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
34,,,O
34,game,B-SKILL_TECH
34,physics,I-SKILL_TECH
34,,,O
34,animation,B-SKILL_TECH
34,pipelines,I-SKILL_TECH
34,,,O
34,shader,B-SKILL_TECH
34,programming,I-SKILL_TECH
34,.,O
34,Ubisoft,B-COMPANY
34,Pune,B-LOCATION

35,SAP,B-JOB_TITLE
35,ABAP,I-JOB_TITLE
35,Consultant,I-JOB_TITLE
35,for,O
35,module,B-SKILL_TECH
35,enhancement,I-SKILL_TECH
35,,,O
35,data,B-SKILL_TECH
35,migration,I-SKILL_TECH
35,,,O
35,report,B-SKILL_TECH
35,development,I-SKILL_TECH
35,and,O
35,debugging,B-SKILL_TECH
35,.,O
35,Siemens,B-COMPANY
35,Bengaluru,B-LOCATION
35,ABAP,B-SKILL_TECH
35,OOP,I-SKILL_TECH
35,preferred,O

36,Business,B-JOB_TITLE
36,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
36,for,O
36,requirements,B-SKILL_TECH
36,documentation,I-SKILL_TECH
36,,,O
36,sprint,B-SKILL_TECH
36,meetings,I-SKILL_TECH
36,,,O
36,backlog,B-SKILL_TECH
36,management,I-SKILL_TECH
36,using,O
36,Jira,B-TOOL
36,.,O
36,SQL,B-SKILL_TECH
36,and,O
36,PowerBI,B-TOOL
36,plus,O
36,.,O
36,Wipro,B-COMPANY
36,Mumbai,B-LOCATION

37,Security,B-JOB_TITLE
37,Pentester,I-JOB_TITLE
37,with,O
37,OWASP,B-SKILL_TECH
37,BurpSuite,B-TOOL
37,Metasploit,B-TOOL
37,Nmap,B-TOOL
37,.,O
37,Deloitte,B-COMPANY
37,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
37,full,B-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE
37,time,I-EMPLOYMENT_TYPE

38,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
38,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
38,build,O
38,ETL,B-SKILL_TECH
38,pipelines,I-SKILL_TECH
38,using,O
38,Apache,B-TOOL
38,Spark,I-TOOL
38,and,O
38,Airflow,B-TOOL
38,.,O
38,AWS,B-TECH_PLATFORM
38,S3,B-TOOL
38,Glue,B-TOOL
38,EMR,B-TOOL
38,required,O
38,.,O
38,Netflix,B-COMPANY
38,Bangalore,B-LOCATION

39,QA,B-JOB_TITLE
39,Automation,I-JOB_TITLE
39,Tester,I-JOB_TITLE
39,with,O
39,Selenium,B-TOOL
39,Cypress,B-TOOL
39,Postman,B-TOOL
39,API,B-SKILL_TECH
39,tests,I-SKILL_TECH
39,,,O
39,regression,B-SKILL_TECH
39,suites,I-SKILL_TECH
39,,,O
39,CI,B-SKILL_TECH
39,pipelines,I-SKILL_TECH
39,.,O
39,Adobe,B-COMPANY
39,Noida,B-LOCATION

40,AI,B-JOB_TITLE
40,Research,I-JOB_TITLE
40,Intern,I-JOB_TITLE
40,with,O
40,transformer,B-SKILL_TECH
40,models,I-SKILL_TECH
40,(,O
40,BERT,B-MODEL
40,GPT,B-MODEL
40,),O
40,TensorFlow,B-FRAMEWORK
40,PyTorch,B-FRAMEWORK
40,.,O
40,Research,B-JOB_TYPE
40,role,O
40,at,O
40,IIT,B-COMPANY
40,Delhi,I-COMPANY
40,campus,O
