sentence_id,token,label
1,We,O
1,are,O
1,looking,O
1,for,O
1,a,O
1,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
1,Scientist,I-JOB_TITLE
1,to,O
1,join,O
1,our,O
1,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
1,office,O
1,.,O
1,The,O
1,ideal,O
1,candidate,O
1,has,O
1,experience,O
1,with,O
1,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
1,",",O
1,SQL,B-TOOL
1,",",O
1,and,O
1,machine,B-SKILL_TECH
1,learning,I-SKILL_TECH
1,frameworks,O
1,like,O
1,TensorFlow,B-FRAMEWORK
1,or,O
1,PyTorch,B-FRAMEWORK
1,.,O
1,Employment,O
1,type,O
1,is,O
1,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
1,.,O
2,Infosys,B-COMPANY
2,is,O
2,hiring,O
2,a,O
2,Software,B-JOB_TITLE
2,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
2,with,O
2,strong,O
2,Java,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
2,and,O
2,Spring,B-FRAMEWORK
2,Framework,I-FRAMEWORK
2,knowledge,O
2,.,O
2,The,O
2,role,O
2,is,O
2,based,O
2,in,O
2,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
2,and,O
2,requires,O
2,good,O
2,communication,B-SKILL_TECH
2,skills,I-SKILL_TECH
2,.,O
2,Employment,O
2,type,O
2,:,O
2,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
2,.,O
3,Amazon,B-COMPANY
3,is,O
3,seeking,O
3,a,O
3,Backend,B-JOB_TITLE
3,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
3,skilled,O
3,in,O
3,Node.js,B-FRAMEWORK
3,",",O
3,AWS,B-TOOL
3,and,O
3,Docker,B-TOOL
3,.,O
3,This,O
3,position,O
3,is,O
3,located,O
3,in,O
3,Chennai,B-LOCATION
3,.,O
3,Candidates,O
3,with,O
3,01-Feb,O
3,years,O
3,of,O
3,experience,O
3,are,O
3,preferred,O
3,.,O
3,Employment,O
3,type,O
3,:,O
3,contract,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
3,.,O
4,We,O
4,need,O
4,a,O
4,Frontend,B-JOB_TITLE
4,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
4,proficient,O
4,in,O
4,React,B-FRAMEWORK
4,",",O
4,JavaScript,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
4,",",O
4,and,O
4,HTML,B-TOOL
4,/,I-TOOL
4,CSS,I-TOOL
4,.,O
4,The,O
4,company,O
4,is,O
4,TCS,B-COMPANY
4,",",O
4,and,O
4,the,O
4,job,O
4,location,O
4,is,O
4,Pune,B-LOCATION
4,.,O
4,Employment,O
4,type,O
4,:,O
4,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
4,.,O
5,Google,B-COMPANY
5,is,O
5,hiring,O
5,a,O
5,Machine,B-JOB_TITLE
5,Learning,I-JOB_TITLE
5,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
5,.,O
5,Required,O
5,skills,O
5,include,O
5,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
5,",",O
5,TensorFlow,B-FRAMEWORK
5,",",O
5,and,O
5,SQL,B-TOOL
5,.,O
5,This,O
5,role,O
5,is,O
5,remote,B-LOCATION
5,.,O
5,Employment,O
5,type,O
5,:,O
5,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
5,.,O
6,Wipro,B-COMPANY
6,is,O
6,looking,O
6,for,O
6,a,O
6,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
6,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
6,skilled,O
6,in,O
6,Excel,B-TOOL
6,",",O
6,Tableau,B-TOOL
6,",",O
6,and,O
6,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
6,.,O
6,The,O
6,role,O
6,is,O
6,based,O
6,in,O
6,Noida,B-LOCATION
6,.,O
6,Employment,O
6,type,O
6,:,O
6,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
6,.,O
7,Job,O
7,location,O
7,:,O
7,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
7,.,O
7,Employment,O
7,type,O
7,:,O
7,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
7,.,O
8,IBM,B-COMPANY
8,is,O
8,hiring,O
8,a,O
8,Cloud,B-JOB_TITLE
8,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
8,experienced,O
8,in,O
8,AWS,B-TOOL
8,",",O
8,Docker,B-TOOL
8,",",O
8,and,O
8,Kubernetes,B-TOOL
8,.,O
8,The,O
8,role,O
8,is,O
8,based,O
8,in,O
8,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
8,.,O
8,Employment,O
8,type,O
8,:,O
8,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
8,.,O
9,Accenture,B-COMPANY
9,seeks,O
9,a,O
9,DevOps,B-JOB_TITLE
9,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
9,skilled,O
9,in,O
9,Jenkins,B-TOOL
9,",",O
9,Git,B-TOOL
9,",",O
9,and,O
9,Linux,B-TOOL
9,.,O
9,The,O
9,job,O
9,is,O
9,located,O
9,in,O
9,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
9,.,O
9,Employment,O
9,type,O
9,:,O
9,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
9,.,O
10,HCL,B-COMPANY
10,is,O
10,looking,O
10,for,O
10,a,O
10,Software,B-JOB_TITLE
10,Tester,I-JOB_TITLE
10,proficient,O
10,in,O
10,Selenium,B-TOOL
10,and,O
10,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
10,.,O
10,This,O
10,role,O
10,is,O
10,based,O
10,in,O
10,Chennai,B-LOCATION
10,.,O
10,Employment,O
10,type,O
10,:,O
10,contract,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
10,.,O
11,We,O
11,are,O
11,hiring,O
11,a,O
11,UI/UX,B-JOB_TITLE
11,Designer,I-JOB_TITLE
11,with,O
11,experience,O
11,in,O
11,Figma,B-TOOL
11,",",O
11,Adobe,B-TOOL
11,XD,I-TOOL
11,",",O
11,and,O
11,prototyping,B-SKILL_TECH
11,tools,I-SKILL_TECH
11,.,O
11,Company,O
11,:,O
11,Zoho,B-COMPANY
11,.,O
11,Location,O
11,:,O
11,Chennai,B-LOCATION
11,.,O
11,Employment,O
11,type,O
11,:,O
11,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
11,.,O
12,Flipkart,B-COMPANY
12,is,O
12,hiring,O
12,a,O
12,Product,B-JOB_TITLE
12,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
12,with,O
12,strong,O
12,soft,B-SKILL_TECH
12,skills,I-SKILL_TECH
12,and,O
12,experience,O
12,in,O
12,market,B-SKILL_TECH
12,analysis,I-SKILL_TECH
12,.,O
12,Location,O
12,:,O
12,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
12,.,O
12,Employment,O
12,type,O
12,:,O
12,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
12,.,O
13,We,O
13,need,O
13,an,O
13,Android,B-JOB_TITLE
13,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
13,with,O
13,Java,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
13,",",O
13,Kotlin,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
13,",",O
13,and,O
13,Android,B-TOOL
13,Studio,I-TOOL
13,expertise,O
13,.,O
13,Company,O
13,:,O
13,Samsung,B-COMPANY
13,.,O
13,Location,O
13,:,O
13,Delhi,B-LOCATION
13,.,O
13,Employment,O
13,type,O
13,:,O
13,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
13,.,O
14,Microsoft,B-COMPANY
14,is,O
14,hiring,O
14,a,O
14,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
14,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
14,skilled,O
14,in,O
14,SQL,B-TOOL
14,",",O
14,Azure,B-TOOL
14,",",O
14,and,O
14,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
14,.,O
14,This,O
14,position,O
14,is,O
14,located,O
14,in,O
14,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
14,.,O
14,Employment,O
14,type,O
14,:,O
14,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
14,.,O
15,We,O
15,are,O
15,looking,O
15,for,O
15,a,O
15,Cybersecurity,B-JOB_TITLE
15,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
15,experienced,O
15,with,O
15,Linux,B-TOOL
15,",",O
15,SIEM,B-TOOL
15,tools,I-TOOL
15,",",O
15,and,O
15,network,B-SKILL_TECH
15,security,I-SKILL_TECH
15,.,O
15,Company,O
15,:,O
15,EY,B-COMPANY
15,.,O
15,Location,O
15,:,O
15,Pune,B-LOCATION
15,.,O
15,Employment,O
15,type,O
15,:,O
15,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
15,.,O
16,Oracle,B-COMPANY
16,is,O
16,hiring,O
16,a,O
16,Database,B-JOB_TITLE
16,Administrator,I-JOB_TITLE
16,with,O
16,strong,O
16,SQL,B-TOOL
16,and,O
16,PL/SQL,B-TOOL
16,knowledge,O
16,.,O
16,Location,O
16,:,O
16,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
16,.,O
16,Employment,O
16,type,O
16,:,O
16,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
16,.,O
17,We,O
17,need,O
17,a,O
17,Mobile,B-JOB_TITLE
17,App,I-JOB_TITLE
17,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
17,with,O
17,Flutter,B-FRAMEWORK
17,",",O
17,Dart,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
17,",",O
17,and,O
17,Firebase,B-TOOL
17,experience,O
17,.,O
17,Company,O
17,:,O
17,Swiggy,B-COMPANY
17,.,O
17,Location,O
17,:,O
17,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
17,.,O
17,Employment,O
17,type,O
17,:,O
17,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
17,.,O
18,We,O
18,are,O
18,looking,O
18,for,O
18,a,O
18,Research,B-JOB_TITLE
18,Intern,I-JOB_TITLE
18,pursuing,O
18,a,O
18,Bachelor's,B-EDUCATION_LEVEL
18,degree,O
18,in,O
18,Computer,B-DEGREE_MAJOR
18,Science,I-DEGREE_MAJOR
18,.,O
18,Company,O
18,:,O
18,Adobe,B-COMPANY
18,.,O
18,Location,O
18,:,O
18,Noida,B-LOCATION
18,.,O
18,Employment,O
18,type,O
18,:,O
18,internship,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
18,.,O
19,Cisco,B-COMPANY
19,is,O
19,hiring,O
19,a,O
19,Network,B-JOB_TITLE
19,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
19,with,O
19,CCNA,B-TOOL
19,certification,O
19,and,O
19,strong,O
19,routing/switching,B-SKILL_TECH
19,knowledge,O
19,.,O
19,Location,O
19,:,O
19,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
19,.,O
19,Employment,O
19,type,O
19,:,O
19,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
19,.,O
20,We,O
20,need,O
20,a,O
20,Full,B-JOB_TITLE
20,Stack,I-JOB_TITLE
20,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
20,experienced,O
20,in,O
20,React,B-FRAMEWORK
20,",",O
20,Node.js,B-FRAMEWORK
20,",",O
20,and,O
20,MongoDB,B-TOOL
20,.,O
20,Company,O
20,:,O
20,Paytm,B-COMPANY
20,.,O
20,Location,O
20,:,O
20,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
20,.,O
20,Employment,O
20,type,O
20,:,O
20,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
20,.,O
21,Meta,B-COMPANY
21,is,O
21,hiring,O
21,an,O
21,AI,B-JOB_TITLE
21,Research,I-JOB_TITLE
21,Scientist,I-JOB_TITLE
21,with,O
21,strong,O
21,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
21,and,O
21,PyTorch,B-FRAMEWORK
21,experience,O
21,.,O
21,Location,O
21,:,O
21,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
21,.,O
21,Employment,O
21,type,O
21,:,O
21,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
21,.,O
22,Tata,B-COMPANY
22,Elxsi,I-COMPANY
22,is,O
22,looking,O
22,for,O
22,an,O
22,Embedded,B-JOB_TITLE
22,Systems,I-JOB_TITLE
22,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
22,skilled,O
22,in,O
22,C,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
22,and,O
22,ARM,B-TOOL
22,controllers,O
22,.,O
22,Location,O
22,:,O
22,Chennai,B-LOCATION
22,.,O
22,Employment,O
22,type,O
22,:,O
22,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
22,.,O
23,Siemens,B-COMPANY
23,seeks,O
23,an,O
23,Automation,B-JOB_TITLE
23,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
23,experienced,O
23,in,O
23,PLC,B-TOOL
23,programming,O
23,and,O
23,SCADA,B-TOOL
23,systems,O
23,.,O
23,Location,O
23,:,O
23,Pune,B-LOCATION
23,.,O
23,Employment,O
23,type,O
23,:,O
23,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
23,.,O
24,Freshworks,B-COMPANY
24,is,O
24,hiring,O
24,a,O
24,Customer,B-JOB_TITLE
24,Success,I-JOB_TITLE
24,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
24,with,O
24,CRM,B-TOOL
24,experience,O
24,.,O
24,Location,O
24,:,O
24,Chennai,B-LOCATION
24,.,O
24,Employment,O
24,type,O
24,:,O
24,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
24,.,O
25,Capgemini,B-COMPANY
25,is,O
25,hiring,O
25,a,O
25,QA,B-JOB_TITLE
25,Automation,I-JOB_TITLE
25,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
25,skilled,O
25,in,O
25,Java,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
25,.,O
25,Location,O
25,:,O
25,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
25,.,O
25,Employment,O
25,type,O
25,:,O
25,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
25,.,O
26,LinkedIn,B-COMPANY
26,is,O
26,looking,O
26,for,O
26,a,O
26,Security,B-JOB_TITLE
26,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
26,with,O
26,cloud,B-SKILL_TECH
26,security,I-SKILL_TECH
26,experience,O
26,.,O
26,Location,O
26,:,O
26,Remote,B-LOCATION
26,.,O
26,Employment,O
26,type,O
26,:,O
26,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
26,.,O
27,Nokia,B-COMPANY
27,seeks,O
27,a,O
27,Telecommunications,B-JOB_TITLE
27,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
27,skilled,O
27,in,O
27,5G,B-SKILL_TECH
27,networks,I-SKILL_TECH
27,and,O
27,RF,B-SKILL_TECH
27,optimization,I-SKILL_TECH
27,.,O
27,Location,O
27,:,O
27,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
27,.,O
27,Employment,O
27,type,O
27,:,O
27,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
27,.,O
28,Byju’s,B-COMPANY
28,is,O
28,hiring,O
28,a,O
28,Content,B-JOB_TITLE
28,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
28,with,O
28,education,B-SKILL_TECH
28,content,I-SKILL_TECH
28,experience,O
28,.,O
28,Location,O
28,:,O
28,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
28,.,O
28,Employment,O
28,type,O
28,:,O
28,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
28,.,O
29,PayPal,B-COMPANY
29,is,O
29,looking,O
29,for,O
29,a,O
29,Backend,B-JOB_TITLE
29,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
29,with,O
29,Java,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
29,and,O
29,AWS,B-TOOL
29,experience,O
29,.,O
29,Location,O
29,:,O
29,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
29,.,O
29,Employment,O
29,type,O
29,:,O
29,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
29,.,O
30,PhonePe,B-COMPANY
30,is,O
30,hiring,O
30,a,O
30,Kotlin,B-JOB_TITLE
30,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
30,with,O
30,Android,B-SKILL_TECH
30,system,I-SKILL_TECH
30,knowledge,O
30,.,O
30,Location,O
30,:,O
30,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
30,.,O
30,Employment,O
30,type,O
30,:,O
30,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
30,.,O
31,Ola,B-COMPANY
31,Electric,I-COMPANY
31,is,O
31,hiring,O
31,an,O
31,EV,B-JOB_TITLE
31,Battery,I-JOB_TITLE
31,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
31,with,O
31,battery,B-SKILL_TECH
31,testing,I-SKILL_TECH
31,experience,O
31,.,O
31,Location,O
31,:,O
31,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
31,.,O
31,Employment,O
31,type,O
31,:,O
31,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
31,.,O
32,Intel,B-COMPANY
32,is,O
32,hiring,O
32,a,O
32,GPU,B-JOB_TITLE
32,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
32,with,O
32,C++,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
32,and,O
32,CUDA,B-TOOL
32,experience,O
32,.,O
32,Location,O
32,:,O
32,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
32,.,O
32,Employment,O
32,type,O
32,:,O
32,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
32,.,O
33,Adobe,B-COMPANY
33,is,O
33,hiring,O
33,a,O
33,Software,B-JOB_TITLE
33,Architect,I-JOB_TITLE
33,with,O
33,microservices,B-SKILL_TECH
33,experience,O
33,.,O
33,Location,O
33,:,O
33,Noida,B-LOCATION
33,.,O
33,Employment,O
33,type,O
33,:,O
33,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
33,.,O
34,KPMG,B-COMPANY
34,is,O
34,hiring,O
34,an,O
34,IT,B-JOB_TITLE
34,Auditor,I-JOB_TITLE
34,with,O
34,SOC,B-TOOL
34,and,O
34,ISO,B-TOOL
34,knowledge,O
34,.,O
34,Location,O
34,:,O
34,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
34,.,O
34,Employment,O
34,type,O
34,:,O
34,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
34,.,O
35,Uber,B-COMPANY
35,is,O
35,hiring,O
35,a,O
35,Maps,B-JOB_TITLE
35,Data,I-JOB_TITLE
35,Specialist,I-JOB_TITLE
35,with,O
35,GIS,B-TOOL
35,skills,O
35,.,O
35,Location,O
35,:,O
35,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
35,.,O
35,Employment,O
35,type,O
35,:,O
35,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
35,.,O
36,Zomato,B-COMPANY
36,is,O
36,hiring,O
36,a,O
36,Delivery,B-JOB_TITLE
36,Operations,I-JOB_TITLE
36,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
36,with,O
36,logistics,B-SKILL_TECH
36,experience,O
36,.,O
36,Location,O
36,:,O
36,Delhi,B-LOCATION
36,.,O
36,Employment,O
36,type,O
36,:,O
36,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
36,.,O
37,Tata,B-COMPANY
37,Steel,I-COMPANY
37,is,O
37,hiring,O
37,a,O
37,Mechanical,B-JOB_TITLE
37,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
37,with,O
37,AutoCAD,B-TOOL
37,experience,O
37,.,O
37,Location,O
37,:,O
37,Jamshedpur,B-LOCATION
37,.,O
37,Employment,O
37,type,O
37,:,O
37,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
37,.,O
38,NICE,B-COMPANY
38,is,O
38,hiring,O
38,a,O
38,Speech,B-JOB_TITLE
38,Scientist,I-JOB_TITLE
38,with,O
38,ASR,B-SKILL_TECH
38,experience,O
38,.,O
38,Location,O
38,:,O
38,Pune,B-LOCATION
38,.,O
38,Employment,O
38,type,O
38,:,O
38,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
38,.,O
39,L, B-COMPANY
39,&,I-COMPANY
39,T,I-COMPANY
39,is,O
39,hiring,O
39,a,O
39,Civil,B-JOB_TITLE
39,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
39,with,O
39,AutoCAD,B-TOOL
39,experience,O
39,.,O
39,Location,O
39,:,O
39,Delhi,B-LOCATION
39,.,O
39,Employment,O
39,type,O
39,:,O
39,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
39,.,O
40,ABB,B-COMPANY
40,is,O
40,hiring,O
40,an,O
40,Electrical,B-JOB_TITLE
40,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
40,with,O
40,power,B-SKILL_TECH
40,automation,I-SKILL_TECH
40,experience,O
40,.,O
40,Location,O
40,:,O
40,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
40,.,O
40,Employment,O
40,type,O
40,:,O
40,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
40,.,O
41,Qualcomm,B-COMPANY
41,is,O
41,hiring,O
41,a,O
41,Firmware,B-JOB_TITLE
41,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
41,with,O
41,C,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
41,and,O
41,RTOS,B-TOOL
41,experience,O
41,.,O
41,Location,O
41,:,O
41,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
41,.,O
41,Employment,O
41,type,O
41,:,O
41,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
41,.,O
42,BharatPe,B-COMPANY
42,is,O
42,hiring,O
42,a,O
42,Financial,B-JOB_TITLE
42,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
42,with,O
42,Excel,B-TOOL
42,skills,O
42,.,O
42,Location,O
42,:,O
42,Delhi,B-LOCATION
42,.,O
42,Employment,O
42,type,O
42,:,O
42,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
42,.,O
43,Havells,B-COMPANY
43,is,O
43,hiring,O
43,an,O
43,Industrial,B-JOB_TITLE
43,Designer,I-JOB_TITLE
43,with,O
43,CAD,B-TOOL
43,experience,O
43,.,O
43,Location,O
43,:,O
43,Noida,B-LOCATION
43,.,O
43,Employment,O
43,type,O
43,:,O
43,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
43,.,O
44,Tech,B-COMPANY
44,Mahindra,I-COMPANY
44,is,O
44,hiring,O
44,an,O
44,RPA,B-JOB_TITLE
44,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
44,with,O
44,UiPath,B-TOOL
44,experience,O
44,.,O
44,Location,O
44,:,O
44,Pune,B-LOCATION
44,.,O
44,Employment,O
44,type,O
44,:,O
44,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
44,.,O
45,Sony,B-COMPANY
45,is,O
45,hiring,O
45,a,O
45,Computer,B-JOB_TITLE
45,Vision,I-JOB_TITLE
45,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
45,with,O
45,OpenCV,B-TOOL
45,and,O
45,Python,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
45,experience,O
45,.,O
45,Location,O
45,:,O
45,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
45,.,O
45,Employment,O
45,type,O
45,:,O
45,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
45,.,O
46,Myntra,B-COMPANY
46,is,O
46,hiring,O
46,a,O
46,Fashion,B-JOB_TITLE
46,Consultant,I-JOB_TITLE
46,with,O
46,industry,B-SKILL_TECH
46,experience,O
46,.,O
46,Location,O
46,:,O
46,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
46,.,O
46,Employment,O
46,type,O
46,:,O
46,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
46,.,O
47,Infosys,B-COMPANY
47,BPM,I-COMPANY
47,is,O
47,hiring,O
47,a,O
47,Process,B-JOB_TITLE
47,Associate,I-JOB_TITLE
47,with,O
47,Excel,B-TOOL
47,experience,O
47,.,O
47,Location,O
47,:,O
47,Pune,B-LOCATION
47,.,O
47,Employment,O
47,type,O
47,:,O
47,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
47,.,O
48,Accolite,B-COMPANY
48,is,O
48,hiring,O
48,a,O
48,Golang,B-JOB_TITLE
48,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
48,with,O
48,API,B-SKILL_TECH
48,experience,O
48,.,O
48,Location,O
48,:,O
48,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
48,.,O
48,Employment,O
48,type,O
48,:,O
48,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
48,.,O
49,DXC,B-COMPANY
49,is,O
49,hiring,O
49,a,O
49,IT,B-JOB_TITLE
49,Support,I-JOB_TITLE
49,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
49,with,O
49,Linux,B-TOOL
49,and,O
49,Networking,B-SKILL_TECH
49,experience,O
49,.,O
49,Location,O
49,:,O
49,Chennai,B-LOCATION
49,.,O
49,Employment,O
49,type,O
49,:,O
49,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
49,.,O
50,Zoho,B-COMPANY
50,is,O
50,hiring,O
50,a,O
50,Technical,B-JOB_TITLE
50,Writer,I-JOB_TITLE
50,with,O
50,documentation,B-SKILL_TECH
50,experience,O
50,.,O
50,Location,O
50,:,O
50,Chennai,B-LOCATION
50,.,O
50,Employment,O
50,type,O
50,:,O
50,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
50,.,O
51,EY,B-COMPANY
51,is,O
51,hiring,O
51,a,O
51,Cloud,B-JOB_TITLE
51,Architect,I-JOB_TITLE
51,with,O
51,Azure,B-TOOL
51,experience,O
51,.,O
51,Location,O
51,:,O
51,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
51,.,O
51,Employment,O
51,type,O
51,:,O
51,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
51,.,O
52,Samsung,B-COMPANY
52,is,O
52,hiring,O
52,a,O
52,Firmware,B-JOB_TITLE
52,Tester,I-JOB_TITLE
52,with,O
52,embedded,B-SKILL_TECH
52,testing,I-SKILL_TECH
52,experience,O
52,.,O
52,Location,O
52,:,O
52,Noida,B-LOCATION
52,.,O
52,Employment,O
52,type,O
52,:,O
52,contract,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
52,.,O
53,Mindtree,B-COMPANY
53,is,O
53,hiring,O
53,a,O
53,Python,B-JOB_TITLE
53,Automation,I-JOB_TITLE
53,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
53,with,O
53,scripting,B-SKILL_TECH
53,experience,O
53,.,O
53,Location,O
53,:,O
53,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
53,.,O
53,Employment,O
53,type,O
53,:,O
53,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
53,.,O
54,Oracle,B-COMPANY
54,is,O
54,hiring,O
54,a,O
54,Linux,B-JOB_TITLE
54,Systems,I-JOB_TITLE
54,Administrator,I-JOB_TITLE
54,with,O
54,shell,B-SKILL_TECH
54,scripting,I-SKILL_TECH
54,experience,O
54,.,O
54,Location,O
54,:,O
54,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
54,.,O
54,Employment,O
54,type,O
54,:,O
54,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
54,.,O
55,Infosys,B-COMPANY
55,is,O
55,hiring,O
55,a,O
55,Blockchain,B-JOB_TITLE
55,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
55,with,O
55,Solidity,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
55,experience,O
55,.,O
55,Location,O
55,:,O
55,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
55,.,O
55,Employment,O
55,type,O
55,:,O
55,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
55,.,O
56,Airtel,B-COMPANY
56,is,O
56,hiring,O
56,a,O
56,Telecom,B-JOB_TITLE
56,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
56,with,O
56,VoLTE,B-SKILL_TECH
56,experience,O
56,.,O
56,Location,O
56,:,O
56,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
56,.,O
56,Employment,O
56,type,O
56,:,O
56,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
56,.,O
57,Dunzo,B-COMPANY
57,is,O
57,hiring,O
57,a,O
57,Logistics,B-JOB_TITLE
57,Planner,I-JOB_TITLE
57,with,O
57,forecasting,B-SKILL_TECH
57,skills,O
57,.,O
57,Location,O
57,:,O
57,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
57,.,O
57,Employment,O
57,type,O
57,:,O
57,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
57,.,O
58,Boston,B-COMPANY
58,Consulting,I-COMPANY
58,Group,I-COMPANY
58,is,O
58,hiring,O
58,an,O
58,IT,B-JOB_TITLE
58,Strategy,I-JOB_TITLE
58,Associate,I-JOB_TITLE
58,with,O
58,research,B-SKILL_TECH
58,experience,O
58,.,O
58,Location,O
58,:,O
58,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
58,.,O
58,Employment,O
58,type,O
58,:,O
58,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
58,.,O
59,CRED,B-COMPANY
59,is,O
59,hiring,O
59,an,O
59,SRE,B-JOB_TITLE
59,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
59,with,O
59,Kubernetes,B-TOOL
59,and,O
59,Grafana,B-TOOL
59,experience,O
59,.,O
59,Location,O
59,:,O
59,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
59,.,O
59,Employment,O
59,type,O
59,:,O
59,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
59,.,O
60,TCS,B-COMPANY
60,is,O
60,hiring,O
60,a,O
60,COBOL,B-JOB_TITLE
60,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
60,for,O
60,banking,B-SKILL_TECH
60,modernization,I-SKILL_TECH
60,projects,O
60,.,O
60,Location,O
60,:,O
60,Chennai,B-LOCATION
60,.,O
60,Employment,O
60,type,O
60,:,O
60,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
60,.,O
61,GE,B-COMPANY
61,Healthcare,I-COMPANY
61,is,O
61,hiring,O
61,a,O
61,Biomedical,B-JOB_TITLE
61,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
61,with,O
61,diagnostic,B-SKILL_TECH
61,equipment,I-SKILL_TECH
61,experience,O
61,.,O
61,Location,O
61,:,O
61,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
61,.,O
61,Employment,O
61,type,O
61,:,O
61,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
61,.,O
62,PwC,B-COMPANY
62,is,O
62,hiring,O
62,a,O
62,Cyber,B-JOB_TITLE
62,Governance,I-JOB_TITLE
62,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
62,with,O
62,ISO,B-TOOL
62,27001,I-TOOL
62,experience,O
62,.,O
62,Location,O
62,:,O
62,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
62,.,O
62,Employment,O
62,type,O
62,:,O
62,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
62,.,O
63,HP,B-COMPANY
63,is,O
63,hiring,O
63,a,O
63,Printer,B-JOB_TITLE
63,Firmware,I-JOB_TITLE
63,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
63,with,O
63,embedded,B-SKILL_TECH
63,C,I-SKILL_TECH
63,experience,O
63,.,O
63,Location,O
63,:,O
63,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
63,.,O
63,Employment,O
63,type,O
63,:,O
63,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
63,.,O
64,Amazon,B-COMPANY
64,is,O
64,hiring,O
64,a,O
64,Warehouse,B-JOB_TITLE
64,Supervisor,I-JOB_TITLE
64,with,O
64,operations,B-SKILL_TECH
64,experience,O
64,.,O
64,Location,O
64,:,O
64,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
64,.,O
64,Employment,O
64,type,O
64,:,O
64,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
64,.,O
65,Walmart,B-COMPANY
65,is,O
65,hiring,O
65,a,O
65,Big,B-JOB_TITLE
65,Data,I-JOB_TITLE
65,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
65,with,O
65,Spark,B-TOOL
65,and,O
65,Hadoop,B-TOOL
65,experience,O
65,.,O
65,Location,O
65,:,O
65,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
65,.,O
65,Employment,O
65,type,O
65,:,O
65,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
65,.,O
66,Jio,B-COMPANY
66,is,O
66,hiring,O
66,a,O
66,Telecom,B-JOB_TITLE
66,Technician,I-JOB_TITLE
66,with,O
66,fiber,B-SKILL_TECH
66,splicing,I-SKILL_TECH
66,knowledge,O
66,.,O
66,Location,O
66,:,O
66,Delhi,B-LOCATION
66,.,O
66,Employment,O
66,type,O
66,:,O
66,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
66,.,O
67,SAP,B-COMPANY
67,Labs,I-COMPANY
67,is,O
67,hiring,O
67,an,O
67,ABAP,B-JOB_TITLE
67,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
67,with,O
67,Fiori,B-TOOL
67,exposure,O
67,.,O
67,Location,O
67,:,O
67,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
67,.,O
67,Employment,O
67,type,O
67,:,O
67,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
67,.,O
68,Dell,B-COMPANY
68,is,O
68,hiring,O
68,a,O
68,Product,B-JOB_TITLE
68,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
68,with,O
68,dashboarding,B-SKILL_TECH
68,experience,O
68,.,O
68,Location,O
68,:,O
68,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
68,.,O
68,Employment,O
68,type,O
68,:,O
68,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
68,.,O
69,Swiggy,B-COMPANY
69,Instamart,I-COMPANY
69,is,O
69,hiring,O
69,a,O
69,Category,B-JOB_TITLE
69,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
69,with,O
69,supplier,B-SKILL_TECH
69,management,I-SKILL_TECH
69,skills,O
69,.,O
69,Location,O
69,:,O
69,Chennai,B-LOCATION
69,.,O
69,Employment,O
69,type,O
69,:,O
69,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
69,.,O
70,ZS,B-COMPANY
70,Associates,I-COMPANY
70,is,O
70,hiring,O
70,a,O
70,Data,B-JOB_TITLE
70,Visualization,I-JOB_TITLE
70,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
70,with,O
70,Tableau,B-TOOL
70,experience,O
70,.,O
70,Location,O
70,:,O
70,Pune,B-LOCATION
70,.,O
70,Employment,O
70,type,O
70,:,O
70,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
70,.,O
71,Tata,B-COMPANY
71,Power,I-COMPANY
71,is,O
71,hiring,O
71,an,O
71,Electrical,B-JOB_TITLE
71,Site,I-JOB_TITLE
71,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
71,.,O
71,Location,O
71,:,O
71,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
71,.,O
71,Employment,O
71,type,O
71,:,O
71,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
71,.,O
72,Cisco,B-COMPANY
72,is,O
72,hiring,O
72,a,O
72,SOC,B-JOB_TITLE
72,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
72,with,O
72,SIEM,B-TOOL
72,experience,O
72,.,O
72,Location,O
72,:,O
72,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
72,.,O
72,Employment,O
72,type,O
72,:,O
72,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
72,.,O
73,CGI,B-COMPANY
73,is,O
73,hiring,O
73,a,O
73,Manual,B-JOB_TITLE
73,Tester,I-JOB_TITLE
73,with,O
73,functional,B-SKILL_TECH
73,testing,I-SKILL_TECH
73,experience,O
73,.,O
73,Location,O
73,:,O
73,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
73,.,O
73,Employment,O
73,type,O
73,:,O
73,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
73,.,O
74,EPAM,B-COMPANY
74,is,O
74,hiring,O
74,a,O
74,Ruby,B-JOB_TITLE
74,on,I-JOB_TITLE
74,Rails,I-JOB_TITLE
74,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
74,with,O
74,API,B-SKILL_TECH
74,experience,O
74,.,O
74,Location,O
74,:,O
74,Pune,B-LOCATION
74,.,O
74,Employment,O
74,type,O
74,:,O
74,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
74,.,O
75,Flipkart,B-COMPANY
75,is,O
75,hiring,O
75,a,O
75,Marketplace,B-JOB_TITLE
75,Onboarding,I-JOB_TITLE
75,Specialist,I-JOB_TITLE
75,.,O
75,Location,O
75,:,O
75,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
75,.,O
75,Employment,O
75,type,O
75,:,O
75,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
75,.,O
76,IBM,B-COMPANY
76,is,O
76,hiring,O
76,a,O
76,Kubernetes,B-JOB_TITLE
76,Administrator,I-JOB_TITLE
76,with,O
76,cluster,B-SKILL_TECH
76,management,I-SKILL_TECH
76,skills,O
76,.,O
76,Location,O
76,:,O
76,Noida,B-LOCATION
76,.,O
76,Employment,O
76,type,O
76,:,O
76,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
76,.,O
77,Goldman,B-COMPANY
77,Sachs,I-COMPANY
77,is,O
77,hiring,O
77,a,O
77,Quant,B-JOB_TITLE
77,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
77,with,O
77,modelling,B-SKILL_TECH
77,experience,O
77,.,O
77,Location,O
77,:,O
77,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
77,.,O
77,Employment,O
77,type,O
77,:,O
77,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
77,.,O
78,Paytm,B-COMPANY
78,is,O
78,hiring,O
78,a,O
78,Fraud,B-JOB_TITLE
78,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
78,with,O
78,risk,B-SKILL_TECH
78,analysis,I-SKILL_TECH
78,experience,O
78,.,O
78,Location,O
78,:,O
78,Noida,B-LOCATION
78,.,O
78,Employment,O
78,type,O
78,:,O
78,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
78,.,O
79,OYO,B-COMPANY
79,is,O
79,hiring,O
79,a,O
79,Supply,B-JOB_TITLE
79,Acquisition,I-JOB_TITLE
79,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
79,with,O
79,hotel,B-SKILL_TECH
79,operations,I-SKILL_TECH
79,experience,O
79,.,O
79,Location,O
79,:,O
79,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
79,.,O
79,Employment,O
79,type,O
79,:,O
79,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
79,.,O
80,HCL,B-COMPANY
80,is,O
80,hiring,O
80,a,O
80,Network,B-JOB_TITLE
80,Support,I-JOB_TITLE
80,Technician,I-JOB_TITLE
80,with,O
80,TCP/IP,B-SKILL_TECH
80,troubleshooting,I-SKILL_TECH
80,skills,O
80,.,O
80,Location,O
80,:,O
80,Pune,B-LOCATION
80,.,O
80,Employment,O
80,type,O
80,:,O
80,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
80,.,O
81,Capillary,B-COMPANY
81,is,O
81,hiring,O
81,a,O
81,CRM,B-JOB_TITLE
81,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
81,with,O
81,campaign,B-SKILL_TECH
81,tools,I-SKILL_TECH
81,experience,O
81,.,O
81,Location,O
81,:,O
81,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
81,.,O
81,Employment,O
81,type,O
81,:,O
81,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
81,.,O
82,ICE,B-COMPANY
82,is,O
82,hiring,O
82,a,O
82,Cloud,B-JOB_TITLE
82,Ops,I-JOB_TITLE
82,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
82,with,O
82,AWS,B-TOOL
82,and,O
82,Terrraform,B-TOOL
82,experience,O
82,.,O
82,Location,O
82,:,O
82,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
82,.,O
82,Employment,O
82,type,O
82,:,O
82,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
82,.,O
83,Trellix,B-COMPANY
83,is,O
83,hiring,O
83,a,O
83,Malware,B-JOB_TITLE
83,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
83,with,O
83,reverse,B-SKILL_TECH
83,engineering,I-SKILL_TECH
83,experience,O
83,.,O
83,Location,O
83,:,O
83,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
83,.,O
83,Employment,O
83,type,O
83,:,O
83,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
83,.,O
84,Nutanix,B-COMPANY
84,is,O
84,hiring,O
84,a,O
84,Virtualization,B-JOB_TITLE
84,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
84,with,O
84,VMware,B-TOOL
84,experience,O
84,.,O
84,Location,O
84,:,O
84,Pune,B-LOCATION
84,.,O
84,Employment,O
84,type,O
84,:,O
84,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
84,.,O
85,Meesho,B-COMPANY
85,is,O
85,hiring,O
85,a,O
85,Supplier,B-JOB_TITLE
85,Relationship,I-JOB_TITLE
85,Specialist,I-JOB_TITLE
85,.,O
85,Location,O
85,:,O
85,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
85,.,O
85,Employment,O
85,type,O
85,:,O
85,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
85,.,O
86,ServiceNow,B-COMPANY
86,is,O
86,hiring,O
86,a,O
86,Platform,B-JOB_TITLE
86,Specialist,I-JOB_TITLE
86,with,O
86,workflow,B-SKILL_TECH
86,configuration,I-SKILL_TECH
86,experience,O
86,.,O
86,Location,O
86,:,O
86,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
86,.,O
86,Employment,O
86,type,O
86,:,O
86,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
86,.,O
87,JPMorgan,B-COMPANY
87,is,O
87,hiring,O
87,a,O
87,Java,B-JOB_TITLE
87,Microservices,I-JOB_TITLE
87,Lead,I-JOB_TITLE
87,with,O
87,architecture,B-SKILL_TECH
87,experience,O
87,.,O
87,Location,O
87,:,O
87,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
87,.,O
87,Employment,O
87,type,O
87,:,O
87,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
87,.,O
88,American,B-COMPANY
88,Express,I-COMPANY
88,is,O
88,hiring,O
88,a,O
88,Credit,B-JOB_TITLE
88,Risk,I-JOB_TITLE
88,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
88,with,O
88,SQL,B-TOOL
88,exposure,O
88,.,O
88,Location,O
88,:,O
88,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
88,.,O
88,Employment,O
88,type,O
88,:,O
88,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
88,.,O
89,OLA,B-COMPANY
89,Cabs,I-COMPANY
89,is,O
89,hiring,O
89,a,O
89,Geographic,B-JOB_TITLE
89,Data,I-JOB_TITLE
89,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
89,.,O
89,Location,O
89,:,O
89,Pune,B-LOCATION
89,.,O
89,Employment,O
89,type,O
89,:,O
89,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
89,.,O
90,Adobe,B-COMPANY
90,is,O
90,hiring,O
90,a,O
90,DevSecOps,B-JOB_TITLE
90,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
90,with,O
90,security,B-SKILL_TECH
90,automation,I-SKILL_TECH
90,experience,O
90,.,O
90,Location,O
90,:,O
90,Noida,B-LOCATION
90,.,O
90,Employment,O
90,type,O
90,:,O
90,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
90,.,O
91,Accenture,B-COMPANY
91,is,O
91,hiring,O
91,a,O
91,VMWare,B-JOB_TITLE
91,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
91,with,O
91,virtualization,B-SKILL_TECH
91,experience,O
91,.,O
91,Location,O
91,:,O
91,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
91,.,O
91,Employment,O
91,type,O
91,:,O
91,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
91,.,O
92,Airtel,B-COMPANY
92,Payments,I-COMPANY
92,Bank,I-COMPANY
92,is,O
92,hiring,O
92,a,O
92,Fraud,B-JOB_TITLE
92,Monitoring,I-JOB_TITLE
92,Specialist,I-JOB_TITLE
92,with,O
92,risk,B-SKILL_TECH
92,analysis,I-SKILL_TECH
92,experience,O
92,.,O
92,Location,O
92,:,O
92,Delhi,B-LOCATION
92,.,O
92,Employment,O
92,type,O
92,:,O
92,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
92,.,O
93,LTIMindtree,B-COMPANY
93,is,O
93,hiring,O
93,an,O
93,API,B-JOB_TITLE
93,Automation,I-JOB_TITLE
93,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
93,with,O
93,scripting,B-SKILL_TECH
93,experience,O
93,.,O
93,Location,O
93,:,O
93,Chennai,B-LOCATION
93,.,O
93,Employment,O
93,type,O
93,:,O
93,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
93,.,O
94,FedEx,B-COMPANY
94,is,O
94,hiring,O
94,a,O
94,Logistics,B-JOB_TITLE
94,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
94,with,O
94,planning,B-SKILL_TECH
94,experience,O
94,.,O
94,Location,O
94,:,O
94,Pune,B-LOCATION
94,.,O
94,Employment,O
94,type,O
94,:,O
94,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
94,.,O
95,Mahindra,B-COMPANY
95,Logistics,I-COMPANY
95,is,O
95,hiring,O
95,a,O
95,Transport,B-JOB_TITLE
95,Coordinator,I-JOB_TITLE
95,with,O
95,logistics,B-SKILL_TECH
95,experience,O
95,.,O
95,Location,O
95,:,O
95,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
95,.,O
95,Employment,O
95,type,O
95,:,O
95,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
95,.,O
96,Bosch,B-COMPANY
96,is,O
96,hiring,O
96,a,O
96,MATLAB,B-JOB_TITLE
96,Simulink,I-JOB_TITLE
96,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
96,with,O
96,simulation,B-SKILL_TECH
96,knowledge,O
96,.,O
96,Location,O
96,:,O
96,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
96,.,O
96,Employment,O
96,type,O
96,:,O
96,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
96,.,O
97,Rapido,B-COMPANY
97,is,O
97,hiring,O
97,a,O
97,Rider,B-JOB_TITLE
97,Operations,I-JOB_TITLE
97,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
97,with,O
97,mobility,B-SKILL_TECH
97,experience,O
97,.,O
97,Location,O
97,:,O
97,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
97,.,O
97,Employment,O
97,type,O
97,:,O
97,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
97,.,O
98,Nestle,B-COMPANY
98,is,O
98,hiring,O
98,a,O
98,Supply,B-JOB_TITLE
98,Chain,I-JOB_TITLE
98,Planner,I-JOB_TITLE
98,with,O
98,forecasting,B-SKILL_TECH
98,knowledge,O
98,.,O
98,Location,O
98,:,O
98,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
98,.,O
98,Employment,O
98,type,O
98,:,O
98,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
98,.,O
99,Philips,B-COMPANY
99,is,O
99,hiring,O
99,a,O
99,QA,B-JOB_TITLE
99,Documentation,I-JOB_TITLE
99,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
99,with,O
99,quality,B-SKILL_TECH
99,process,I-SKILL_TECH
99,experience,O
99,.,O
99,Location,O
99,:,O
99,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
99,.,O
99,Employment,O
99,type,O
99,:,O
99,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
99,.,O
100,HPE,B-COMPANY
100,is,O
100,hiring,O
100,a,O
100,Storage,B-JOB_TITLE
100,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
100,with,O
100,SAN,B-TOOL
100,and,O
100,NAS,B-TOOL
100,experience,O
100,.,O
100,Location,O
100,:,O
100,Chennai,B-LOCATION
100,.,O
100,Employment,O
100,type,O
100,:,O
100,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
100,.,O
101,CitiBank,B-COMPANY
101,is,O
101,hiring,O
101,a,O
101,Business,B-JOB_TITLE
101,Finance,I-JOB_TITLE
101,Associate,I-JOB_TITLE
101,.,O
101,Location,O
101,:,O
101,Mumbai,B-LOCATION
101,.,O
101,Employment,O
101,type,O
101,:,O
101,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
101,.,O
102,Wipro,B-COMPANY
102,is,O
102,hiring,O
102,a,O
102,Scrum,B-JOB_TITLE
102,Master,I-JOB_TITLE
102,with,O
102,Agile,B-SKILL_TECH
102,certification,I-SKILL_TECH
102,.,O
102,Location,O
102,:,O
102,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
102,.,O
102,Employment,O
102,type,O
102,:,O
102,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
102,.,O
103,Infosys,B-COMPANY
103,is,O
103,hiring,O
103,a,O
103,React,B-JOB_TITLE
103,Native,I-JOB_TITLE
103,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
103,.,O
103,Location,O
103,:,O
103,Mysore,B-LOCATION
103,.,O
103,Employment,O
103,type,O
103,:,O
103,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
103,.,O
104,Tech,B-COMPANY
104,Mahindra,I-COMPANY
104,is,O
104,hiring,O
104,a,O
104,Voice,B-JOB_TITLE
104,Process,I-JOB_TITLE
104,Executive,I-JOB_TITLE
104,.,O
104,Location,O
104,:,O
104,Noida,B-LOCATION
104,.,O
104,Employment,O
104,type,O
104,:,O
104,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
104,.,O
105,EY,B-COMPANY
105,is,O
105,hiring,O
105,a,O
105,Tax,B-JOB_TITLE
105,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
105,.,O
105,Location,O
105,:,O
105,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
105,.,O
105,Employment,O
105,type,O
105,:,O
105,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
105,.,O
106,Genpact,B-COMPANY
106,is,O
106,hiring,O
106,a,O
106,Process,B-JOB_TITLE
106,Trainer,I-JOB_TITLE
106,.,O
106,Location,O
106,:,O
106,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
106,.,O
106,Employment,O
106,type,O
106,:,O
106,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
106,.,O
107,Sony,B-COMPANY
107,is,O
107,hiring,O
107,a,O
107,Game,B-JOB_TITLE
107,Physics,I-JOB_TITLE
107,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
107,with,O
107,C++,B-PROGRAMMING_LANGUAGE
107,experience,O
107,.,O
107,Location,O
107,:,O
107,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
107,.,O
107,Employment,O
107,type,O
107,:,O
107,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
107,.,O
108,Cognizant,B-COMPANY
108,is,O
108,hiring,O
108,a,O
108,Power,B-JOB_TITLE
108,BI,I-JOB_TITLE
108,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
108,with,O
108,reporting,B-SKILL_TECH
108,experience,O
108,.,O
108,Location,O
108,:,O
108,Pune,B-LOCATION
108,.,O
108,Employment,O
108,type,O
108,:,O
108,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
108,.,O
109,Shell,B-COMPANY
109,is,O
109,hiring,O
109,an,O
109,Energy,B-JOB_TITLE
109,Analyst,I-JOB_TITLE
109,with,O
109,energy,B-SKILL_TECH
109,forecasting,I-SKILL_TECH
109,experience,O
109,.,O
109,Location,O
109,:,O
109,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
109,.,O
109,Employment,O
109,type,O
109,:,O
109,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
109,.,O
110,Reliance,B-COMPANY
110,Digital,I-COMPANY
110,is,O
110,hiring,O
110,a,O
110,Retail,B-JOB_TITLE
110,Store,I-JOB_TITLE
110,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
110,.,O
110,Location,O
110,:,O
110,Chennai,B-LOCATION
110,.,O
110,Employment,O
110,type,O
110,:,O
110,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
110,.,O
111,HDFC,B-COMPANY
111,Bank,I-COMPANY
111,is,O
111,hiring,O
111,a,O
111,Branch,B-JOB_TITLE
111,Sales,I-JOB_TITLE
111,Officer,I-JOB_TITLE
111,.,O
111,Location,O
111,:,O
111,Delhi,B-LOCATION
111,.,O
111,Employment,O
111,type,O
111,:,O
111,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
111,.,O
112,Infosys,B-COMPANY
112,is,O
112,hiring,O
112,a,O
112,Mulesoft,B-JOB_TITLE
112,Integration,I-JOB_TITLE
112,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
112,.,O
112,Location,O
112,:,O
112,Pune,B-LOCATION
112,.,O
112,Employment,O
112,type,O
112,:,O
112,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
112,.,O
113,Amazon,B-COMPANY
113,is,O
113,hiring,O
113,a,O
113,Financial,B-JOB_TITLE
113,Operations,I-JOB_TITLE
113,Associate,I-JOB_TITLE
113,.,O
113,Location,O
113,:,O
113,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
113,.,O
113,Employment,O
113,type,O
113,:,O
113,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
113,.,O
114,Mercedes-Benz,B-COMPANY
114,is,O
114,hiring,O
114,a,O
114,Vehicle,B-JOB_TITLE
114,Software,I-JOB_TITLE
114,Tester,I-JOB_TITLE
114,.,O
114,Location,O
114,:,O
114,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
114,.,O
114,Employment,O
114,type,O
114,:,O
114,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
114,.,O
115,Axis,B-COMPANY
115,Bank,I-COMPANY
115,is,O
115,hiring,O
115,a,O
115,Relationship,B-JOB_TITLE
115,Manager,I-JOB_TITLE
115,.,O
115,Location,O
115,:,O
115,Gurgaon,B-LOCATION
115,.,O
115,Employment,O
115,type,O
115,:,O
115,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
115,.,O
116,Siemens,B-COMPANY
116,is,O
116,hiring,O
116,an,O
116,Energy,B-JOB_TITLE
116,Management,I-JOB_TITLE
116,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
116,.,O
116,Location,O
116,:,O
116,Noida,B-LOCATION
116,.,O
116,Employment,O
116,type,O
116,:,O
116,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
116,.,O
117,Micron,B-COMPANY
117,is,O
117,hiring,O
117,a,O
117,Memory,B-JOB_TITLE
117,Validation,I-JOB_TITLE
117,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
117,.,O
117,Location,O
117,:,O
117,Hyderabad,B-LOCATION
117,.,O
117,Employment,O
117,type,O
117,:,O
117,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
117,.,O
118,PayPal,B-COMPANY
118,is,O
118,hiring,O
118,a,O
118,Compliance,B-JOB_TITLE
118,Associate,I-JOB_TITLE
118,.,O
118,Location,O
118,:,O
118,Chennai,B-LOCATION
118,.,O
118,Employment,O
118,type,O
118,:,O
118,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
118,.,O
119,Infosys,B-COMPANY
119,is,O
119,hiring,O
119,a,O
119,Vue,B-JOB_TITLE
119,js,I-JOB_TITLE
119,Developer,I-JOB_TITLE
119,.,O
119,Location,O
119,:,O
119,Bangalore,B-LOCATION
119,.,O
119,Employment,O
119,type,O
119,:,O
119,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
119,.,O
120,Google,B-COMPANY
120,is,O
120,hiring,O
120,an,O
120,LLM,B-JOB_TITLE
120,Evaluation,I-JOB_TITLE
120,Engineer,I-JOB_TITLE
120,.,O
120,Location,O
120,:,O
120,Remote,B-LOCATION
120,.,O
120,Employment,O
120,type,O
120,:,O
120,full-time,B-EMPLOYEMENT_TYPE
120,.,O
